(Raj:)What are you drawing over there?
(Sheldon:)A hypothetical containment field
for a Frisbee-sized wormhole...
(Sheldon:)...that could serve as a portal
to a parallel universe.
(Howard:)Oh, you silly doodlebug.
(Leonard:)A lot of scientists believe
making contact with other life-forms...
(Leonard:)...would probably not end well for us.
(Sheldon:)It's a Frisbee-sized wormhole, Leonard.
You could block it with a Frisbee.
Calm down.
Do you expect me to build this? Heh.
(Sheldon:)I expect you to wipe the pudding
off your chin. Gentlemen.
(Howard:)Have you guys ever noticed that Sheldon
always disappears every day at 2:45?
- Really?
- He probably just goes to the bathroom.
Actually, no. He goes at 8 a.m.
With optional follow-ups...
...at 1:45 and 7:10 on high-fiber Fridays.
(Raj:)It's sad that you know that.
(Howard:)Oh...
That's just the tip of the sadness iceberg.
(Howard:)I'm looking at his public calendar.
Two-forty-five to 3:05, nothing.
Yesterday, 2:45 to 3:05, nothing.
(Howard:)Last week, nothing. Last month, nothing.
(Howard:)He never has anything booked
during that time.
(Raj:)Twenty minutes a day
completely unaccounted for.
- We should figure out where he goes.
- Ooh, this is exciting.
(Raj:)Like one of my classic
murder-mystery dinner parties.
(Leonard:)Right, the case of who murdered
three Saturday nights of my life.
Colonel Koothrappali in the kitchen
with the olive spread.
(Raj:)It was tapenade and you guys suck.